Kat, I'm trying to think, is there like an analogy
of liberals invading, I mean, Republicans invading
like a liberal bastion and saying,
if we just hang out here, you know what I mean?
It feels like they're poaching.
They're trying to poach people, but it's not working.
Yeah, I don't feel like Democrats need to go to the gym.
I think they just need to go somewhere.
Right, like I don't feel like it should be that complicated.
Yeah, you're right.
Instead of maybe sitting around
like running analytics on men,
why don't you just go out and meet them?
Right.
Like they're not like mythical creatures in a forest.
You can just go talk to dudes.
Yes, it's not that hard.
It's actually too easy.
Yeah, it is.
It's harder to not talk to dudes than it is to talk to men.
Just unbutton the top button, it works for me.
But they're acting like you need to like create men
in a laboratory and then like run tests on them.
Just go outside, go to a place where people are,
but you have to talk and you also have to listen.
You have to listen without looking for a thing
where it's like, well, actually this thing you said,
you have to just listen.
Yeah, but you know what?
You're saying it's easy to go outside,
but that might be the number one issue
is that they don't like going outside in general.
Well, who does?
Yeah. That's true.